{
			question0: {
                questionText: 'What does HTML stand for?',
                optionOne: 'hyper-text-markup-language',
                optionTwo: 'hyper-text-manufacturing-language',
                optionThree: 'high-texture-manipulation-language',
                optionFour: 'None of these',
                answer: 1,
                pointsOnGuessing:50
            },
            question1: {
                questionText: 'How to create a new two-dimensional array in C# ?',
                optionOne: 'var arr = new Array(2)',
                optionTwo: 'int[,] arr = new int[a,b]',
                optionThree: 'int[,] arr = new int[a][b]',
                optionFour:  'Array.newArray(2)',
                answer: 2,
                pointsOnGuessing: 100
            },
            question2: {
                questionText: 'How is the wrapping of an item as an Object called in C#?',
                optionOne: 'Data compression',
                optionTwo: 'Unboxing',
                optionThree: 'Wrapping',
                optionFour: 'Boxing',
                answer: 4,
                pointsOnGuessing: 150
            },
            question3: {
                questionText: 'Can a C# array contain data from different types?',
                optionOne: 'Yes',
                optionTwo: 'No',
                optionThree: 'Depends of which types of data',
                optionFour: 'Can be calibrated',
                answer: 2,
                pointsOnGuessing: 200
            },      
			question4: {
                questionText: 'What was the original idea of HTML?',
                optionOne: 'Just to transfer small amounts of text data',
                optionTwo: 'To start the Windows 9.8 platform',
                optionThree: 'To make applications easier to write',
                optionFour: 'To encrypt files',
                answer: 1,
                pointsOnGuessing: 250
            },     		
			question5: {
                questionText: 'How can the children of a class able to override the parents methods?',
                optionOne: 'They can not',
                optionTwo: 'Using Regular expressions',
                optionThree: 'Initializing the method in themselves instantly overrides the one from the parent',
                optionFour: 'They can override the method if the parent has set them to "virtual"',
                answer: 4,
                pointsOnGuessing: 300
            },     	
			question6: {
                questionText: 'What is the correct way to validate data,when introducing it to a class?',
                optionOne: 'Validation is not needed',
                optionTwo: 'Validation must be done in the constructor of the class',
                optionThree: 'Data given to the properties must be validated in the properties',
                optionFour: 'Fields should validate the input themselves',
                answer: 3,
                pointsOnGuessing: 500
            },    
			question7: {
                questionText: 'What is the correct way to validate data,when introducing it to a class?',
                optionOne: 'Validation is not needed',
                optionTwo: 'Validation must be done in the constructor of the class',
                optionThree: 'Data given to the properties must be validated in the properties',
                optionFour: 'Fields should validate the input themselves',
                answer: 3,
                pointsOnGuessing: 570
            },   
			question8: {
                questionText: 'What is the correct way to validate data,when introducing it to a class?',
                optionOne: 'Validation is not needed',
                optionTwo: 'Validation must be done in the constructor of the class',
                optionThree: 'Data given to the properties must be validated in the properties',
                optionFour: 'Fields should validate the input themselves',
                answer: 3,
                pointsOnGuessing: 670
            }, 
			question9: {
                questionText: 'What is the correct way to validate data,when introducing it to a class?',
                optionOne: 'Validation is not needed',
                optionTwo: 'Validation must be done in the constructor of the class',
                optionThree: 'Data given to the fields must be validated in the properties',
                optionFour: 'Fields should validate the input themselves',
                answer: 3,
                pointsOnGuessing: 820
            }, 
			question10: {
                questionText: 'What is the correct way to validate data,when introducing it to a class?',
                optionOne: 'Validation is not needed',
                optionTwo: 'Validation must be done in the constructor of the class',
                optionThree: 'Data given to the properties must be validated in the properties',
                optionFour: 'Fields should validate the input themselves',
                answer: 3,
                pointsOnGuessing: 1000
            }, 			
			question11: {
                questionText: 'Which of the following is not a standard part of the class hierarchy?',
                optionOne: 'Field',
                optionTwo: 'Property',
                optionThree: 'Constructor',
                optionFour: 'Emulator',
                answer: 4,
                pointsOnGuessing: 1100
            }, 		
			question12: {
                questionText: 'What C# component acts like a List,but does not allow repeated adding of a element,
				that is already inside?',
                optionOne: 'Two-dimensional array',
                optionTwo: 'Hashset',
                optionThree: 'There is no such thing',
                optionFour: 'The "Object" class',
                answer: 2,
                pointsOnGuessing: 1110
            }, 		

			
}